<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dilli Darshan</string>
    <string name="title_item_detail">Item Detail</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="category_attractions">Attractions</string>

    <string name="title_spot1">Akshardham</string>
    <string name="address_spot1">Noida Mor, Pandav Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi 110092</string>
    <string name="time_spot1">9:30 AM - 6:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot1">\'Akshardham\' means the divine abode of God. It is hailed as an eternal place of devotion, purity and peace.Swaminarayan Akshardham at New Delhi is a Mandir – an abode of God, a Hindu house of worship, and a spiritual and cultural campus dedicated to devotion, learning and harmony. Timeless Hindu spiritual messages, vibrant devotional traditions and ancient architectureall are echoed in its art and architecture.The mandir is a humble tribute to Bhagwan Swaminarayan (1781- 1830), the avatars, devas andgreat sages of Hinduism. The traditionally-styled complex was inaugurated on 6 November 2005 with the blessings of HH Pramukh Swami Maharaj and through the devoted efforts of skilled artisans and volunteers.The Akshardham mandir has over two hundred murtis,representing many of the spiritual stalwarts over many millennia.It has open gardens, water bodies and a step-well styled courtyard.</string>
    <string name="title_spot2">Red Fort</string>
    <string name="address_spot2"> Netaji Subhash Marg, Lal Qila, Chandni Chowk, New Delhi, Delhi 110006</string>
    <string name="time_spot2">9:30 AM - 4:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot2">The Red Fort is a historic fort in the city of Delhi in India that served as the main residence of the Mughal Emperors.Emperor Shah Jahan commissioned reconstruction of the Red Fort on 12 May 1638, when he decided to shift his capital from Agra to Delhi.Originally red and white, its design is credited to architect it was reconstructed between May 1639 and April 1648. On 15 August 1947,the first prime minister of India, Jawaharlal Nehru, raised the Indian national flag above the Lahori Gate. Every year on India\'sIndependence Day, the prime minister hoists the Indian flag at the fort\'s main gate and delivers a nationally broadcast speech from its ramparts.</string>
    <string name="title_spot3">India Gate</string>
    <string name="address_spot3">Rajpath, India Gate, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="time_spot3">Open 24 hours. Best time : 7:00 PM - 9:30 PM (Light Show)</string>
    <string name="body_spot3">The India Gate is a war memorial located astride the Rajpath, on the eastern edge of the ceremonial axis of New Delhi, formerly called Kingsway. It stands as a memorial to 70,000 soldiers of the British Indian Army who died in between 1914–1921in the First World War, in France, Flanders, Mesopotamia, Persia, East Africa, Gallipoli and elsewhere in the Near and the Far East, and the third Anglo-Afghan War. 13,300 servicemen\'s names, including some soldiers and officers from the United Kingdom, are inscribed on thegate. Designed by Sir Edwin Lutyens, the gate evokes the architectural style of the triumphal arch such as the Arch of Constantine, inRome, and is often compared to the Arc de Triomphe in Paris, and the Gateway of India in Mumbai. Following the Bangladesh Liberation war in 1972, a structure consisting of a black marble plinth with a reversed rifle, capped by a war helmet and bounded by four eternal flames,was built beneath the archway. This structure, called Amar Jawan Jyoti, has since 1971 served as India\'s tomb of the unknown soldier.</string>
    <string name="title_spot4">Qutub Minar</string>
    <string name="address_spot4"> Seth Sarai, Mehrauli, New Delhi, Delhi 110030</string>
    <string name="time_spot4">7:00 AM - 5:00 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot4">The Qutb Minar, also spelled as Qutub Minar and Qutab Minar, is a minaret and "victory tower" that forms part of the Qutb complex, a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the Mehrauli area of Delhi, India. The height of Qutub Minar is 72.5 meters, making it the tallest minaret in the world built of bricks. The tower tapers, and has a 14.3 metres base diameter, reducing to 2.7 metres at the top of the peak. It contains a spiral staircase of 379 steps. Its closest comparator is the 62-metre all-brick Minaret of Jam in Afghanistan, ofc.1190, a decade or so before the probable start of the Delhi tower. The surfaces of both are elaborately decorated with inscriptions and geometric patterns; in Delhi the shaft is fluted with "superb stalactite bracketing under the balconies" at the top of each stage. In general minarets were slow to be used in India, and are often detached from the main mosque where they exist. </string>
    <string name="title_spot5">Lotus Temple</string>
    <string name="address_spot5"> Lotus Temple Rd, Bahapur, Shambhu Dayal Bagh, Kalkaji, New Delhi, Delhi 110019</string>
    <string name="time_spot5">9:00 AM - 5:00 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot5">The Lotus Temple, located in Delhi, India, is a Baháʼí House of Worship that was dedicated in December 1986. Notable for its flower like shape, it has become a prominent attraction in the city. Like all Baháʼí Houses of Worship, the Lotus Temple is open to all, regardless of religion or any other qualification. The building is composed of 27 free-standing marble-clad "petals" arranged in clusters of three to form nine sides, with nine doors opening onto a central hall with a height of slightly over 34.27 metres and a capacity of 2,500 people. The Lotus Temple has won numerous architectural awards and has been featured in many newspaper and magazine articles. A 2001 CNN report referred to it as the most visited building in the world.</string>
    <string name="title_spot6">Rashtrapati Bhavan</string>
    <string name="address_spot6">Rashtrapati Bhawan, President\'s Estate, New Delhi, Delhi 110004</string>
    <string name="time_spot6">9:30 AM - 5:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot6">The Rashtrapati Bhavan is the official residence of the President of India located at the Western end of Rajpath in New Delhi,India. Rashtrapati Bhavan may refer to only the 340-room main building that has the president\'s official residence, including reception halls, guest rooms and offices, also called the mansion; it may also refer to the entire 130-hectare Presidential Estate that additionally includes huge presidential gardens, large open spaces, residences of bodyguards and staff, stables, other offices and utilities within its perimeter walls.In terms of area, it is the largest residence of any head of state in the world.</string>
    <string name="title_spot7">Jama Masjid</string>
    <string name="address_spot7">Jama Masjid Rd, Jama Masjid, Chandni Chowk, New Delhi, Delhi 110006</string>
    <string name="time_spot7">7:00 AM - 12:00 PM  ,  1:30 PM - 6:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot7">The Masjid e Jahan Numa, commonly known as the Jama Masjid of Delhi, is one of the largest mosques in India. It was built by the Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan between 1650 and 1656 at a cost of one million rupees, and was inaugurated by Imam Syed Abdul Ghafoor Shah Bukhari from Bukhara, present-day Uzbekistan. The mosque was completed in 1656 AD with three great gates and two 40 metres high minarets constructed with strips of red sandstone and white marble. The courtyard can accommodate more than 2500 people. There are three domes on the terrace which are surrounded by the two minarets. On the floor, a total of 899 black borders are marked for worshippers. The architectural plan of Badshahi Masjid,built by Shah Jahan\'s son Aurangzeb at Lahore, Pakistan, is similar to the Jama Masjid.</string>
    <string name="title_spot8">Sri Laxmi Narayan Mandir</string>
    <string name="address_spot8">Mandir Marg, Near, Gole Market, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="time_spot8">4:30 AM – 1:30 PM  ,  2:30 – 9:00 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot8">The Laxminarayan Temple, also known as the Birla Mandir is a Hindu temple up to large extent dedicated to Laxminarayan in Delhi,India. Laxminarayan usually refers to Vishnu, Preserver in the Trimurti, also known as Narayan, when he is with his consort Lakshmi. The temple,inaugurated by Mahatma Gandhi, was built by Jugal Kishore Birla from 1933 and 1939. The side temples are dedicated to Shiva, Krishna and Buddha. It was the first large Hindu temple built in Delhi. The temple is spread over 7.5 acres, adorned with many shrines, fountains, and a large garden with Hindu and Nationalistic sculptures, and also houses Geeta Bhawan for discourses. The temple is one of the major attractions of Delhi and attracts thousands of devotees on the festivals of Janmashtami and Diwali.</string>
    <string name="title_spot9">Sri Bangla Sahib Gurudwara</string>
    <string name="address_spot9">Hanuman Road Area, Connaught Place, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="time_spot9">Open 24 hours</string>
    <string name="body_spot9">Gurudwara Bangla Sahib is one of the most prominent Sikh gurdwara, or Sikh house of worship, in Delhi, India and known for its association with the eighth Sikh Guru, Guru Har Krishan, as well as the holy river inside its complex, known as the "Sarovar." It was first built as a small shrine by Sikh General Sardar Baghel Singh in 1783, who supervised the construction of nine Sikh shrines in Delhi in the same year, during thereign of Mughal Emperor, Shah Alam II. It is situated near Connaught Place, New Delhi on Baba Kharak Singh Marg and it is instantly recognisable by its golden dome and tall flagpole, Nishan Sahib. Located next to it is the Sacred Heart Cathedral.</string>
    <string name="title_spot10">Humayun’s Tomb</string>
    <string name="address_spot10"> Mathura Road Opposite, Hazrat Nizamuddin Aulia Dargah, Nizamuddin, New Delhi, Delhi 110013</string>
    <string name="time_spot10">8:00 AM - 6:00PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot10">Humayun\'s tomb is the tomb of the Mughal Emperor Humayun in Delhi, India. The tomb was commissioned by Humayun\'s first wife and chief consort, Empress Bega Begum, in 1569-70, and designed by Mirak Mirza Ghiyas and his son, Sayyid Muhammad, Persian architects chosen by her. It was the first garden-tomb on the Indian subcontinent, and is located in Nizamuddin East, Delhi, India, close to the Dina-panah Citadel, also known as Purana Qila, that Humayun found in 1533. It was also the first structure to use red sandstone at such a scale. The tomb was declared a UNESCO World Heritage Site in 1993, and since then has undergone extensive restoration work, which is complete. Besides the main tomb enclosure of Humayun, several smaller monuments dot the pathway leading up to it, from the main entrance in the West, including one that even pre-dates the main tomb itself, by twenty years;it is the tomb complex of Isa Khan Niyazi, an Afghan noble in Sher Shah Suri\'s court of the Suri dynasty, who fought against the Mughals, constructed in 1547 CE.</string>
    <string name="title_spot11">Adventure Island</string>
    <string name="address_spot11">Opposite Rithala Metro Station, Sector 10, Rohini, Delhi, 110085</string>
    <string name="time_spot11">11:00 AM - 7:00 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot11">Adventure Island is an amusement park in Metro Walk Mall. Family-friendly theme park with water coasters, boats and rides, plus a putting green and jungle maze.</string>
    <string name="title_spot12">Fun N Food Village</string>
    <string name="address_spot12">Old Delhi Gurgaon Rd, Kapas Hera, New Delhi, Delhi 110097</string>
    <string name="time_spot12">10:00 AM - 7:00 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot12">As a member of the World Water Park Association, USA. the Fun N Food Village offers India\'s largest collection of Water slides and attractions for the toddler learning how to swim to the Water sports enthusiast seeking a thrill.Thrills, chills and spills … don\'t miss them at the Fun n Food Village offers its patrons a new twisting turning and sliding experience.Fun \'N\' Food Village is offering a fusion of Amusement Park Rides. Amusement park with 21 amusement rides, landscaped gardens, multi cuisine food outlets.The Fun \'N\' Food Village, located just three kilometers from the International airport on the Old Delhi Gurgaon Road. The Fun \'N\' Food Village is an endeavor to create a fusion of our rich Indian legacy and modern recreational facilities. At the Fun \'N\' Food Village, we have many Amusement rides of international standards catering to all age groups.</string>
    <string name="title_spot13">National Zoological Park</string>
    <string name="address_spot13"> Mathura Rd, Pragati Maidan, New Delhi, Delhi 110003</string>
    <string name="time_spot13">9:00 AM - 4:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot13">The National Zoological Park is a 176-acre zoo in New Delhi, India. A 16th-century citadel, a sprawling green island and a motley collection of animals and birds, all in the middle of a burgeoning urban Delhi. The zoo is home to about 1350 animals representing almost 130 species of animals and birds from around the world.It is home to some white tigers also. The zoo can be seen on foot or using a battery-operated vehicle which can be rented at the zoo. Visitors are not permitted to bring any food other than drinking water, but there is a canteen in the zoo.</string>
    <string name="title_spot14">Splash The Water Park</string>
    <string name="address_spot14"> Main GT Karnal Road, Near Palla Moad, Alipur, New Delhi, Delhi 110036</string>
    <string name="time_spot14">10:00 AM - 7:00 PM</string>
    <string name="body_spot14">Spread over an area of 5 acres, Splash is an ideal cross between an amusement park and a water park. Comprising of a variety of water and joy rides, the park offers hours of fun for children and adults alike. Splash remains open for 10 months a year, starting from March 1 and apart from the usual daytime rides, the park also opens up for special night events for which tickets need to be purchased separately. In order to take better care of your belongings, there is a locker facility available at the park. Also, you can get swimming costumes and other necessary gear for rent in case you forget to carry your own. There is a provision of exclusive packages for schools, institutes, and even corporates. These packages vary in price range but essentially,consist of a combination of water and joy rides, welcome drinks, food and return gifts. </string>

    <string name="title_food1">Indian Accent</string>
    <string name="address_food1">The Lodhi, Lodhi Rd, CGO Complex, Pragati Vihar, New Delhi, Delhi 110003</string>
    <string name="phone_food1">+919871117968</string>
    <string name="time_food1">12:00 PM – 2:30PM  ,  7:00 PM - 11:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_food1">Contemporary twists on Indian cuisine served at Indian Accent with glass walls and ceilings.Indian Accent showcases inventive Indian cuisine by complementing the flavours and traditions of India with global ingredients and techniques.Indian food is considered to be rich and covered in gravy. But Indian Accent has changed all that and created a new definition of our cuisine. The modern avatar of Indian dishes generated by chef Manish Mehrotra are a revelation. He is a genius who tries to give his regulars a change every week. He is innovative and keeps within bounds of the authenticity offering dishes like pulled kathal phulka taco which is essentially a jackfruit wrap.</string>
    <string name="title_food2">Barbeque Nation </string>
    <string name="address_food2">N-96, 2nd Floor, Munshi Lal Building, Connaught Place, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="phone_food2">+918061756005</string>
    <string name="time_food2">11:30 AM – 7:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_food2">We were so much into American food that we forgot our authentic delicious Seekhs Kababs and Tikkas; the sizzle of meat as it hits the hot grill is something that leaves your mouth-watering. Barbeque Nation is a big marvelous chain of restaurants who has bought a culinary storm of food evolution. It has brought with it an era of all-you-can-eat concept and live grills. We know this popular brand to be a major hub for large scale dining along with a center of the delicious food.Barbeque Nation focusses more on Chinese, North-Indian and Mediterranean. It is better to opt for buffet spread which is quite lavish here as dining at Barbeque Nation is not so cheap. Food served here are so finger- licking that first, you will first eat it with your eyes and then mouth. Try out: Paneer Tikka, Peshawari Chicken Tikka, Cajun Spicy Baby Potato, Mutton Seekh Kabab, Noodles, Biryani followed by some delectable desserts like Gulab Jamun, Pudding and Pastries. Barbeque Nation has outlets all over the city like Saket, Sector 16 Noida, Sushant Lok, Janakpuri, Netaji Subhash Place, Vivek Vihar, Jangpura, Vasant Kunj, Sohna Road, Faridabad and even in the heart of Delhi, Connaught Place.</string>
    <string name="title_food3">Baluchi</string>
    <string name="address_food3">2nd Floor, Barakhamba Rd, Fire Brigade Lane, Connaught Place, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="phone_food3"> 011 4444 7777</string>
    <string name="time_food3">12:00 PM to 03:00 PM  ,  07:30 PM - 11:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_food3">Placed at the Barakhamba Avenue on Barakhamba Road, New Delhi is Baluchi, a luxurious fine dining restaurant. Due to its prime location and prevailing reputation, Baluchi is a much frequented dining option with families, business associates and foodies. The restaurant is popular amongst the culinary circuit for its exceptional cooking and affluent interiors.The interiors of Baluchi are beautifully designed and every inch of the space shouts money.Baluchi is counted as one of the most loveliest restaurants in the city and is called a complete package. A spectacular wine library stands on one corner of the restaurant, beckoning you to indulge. Although quite expensive, dining at Baluchi doesn\'t pinch much when you consider its brilliant cooking and even marvellous menu, that forays into Mughlai, South-Indian and North-Indian cuisine. Begin with a refreshing glass of ganne ka ras before hitting the appetizers section. Tuck into their, malai artichoke, pomfret hara masala, ajwaini paneer tikka, gilafi murgh ke seekh, bhuttey ke kebab, raan-e-dum Baluchi, dahi aur sing daney ke kebab, dill salmon tikka and Awadhi kalmi kebab. You are recommended to save some appetite for the main course, for it is fantastic. You should try out dishes like, murgh Balti yakhni, vegetable khurma, afghani nalli nihari, govind gatta curry, kozhi poondu masala. Each dish comes with a wine pairing recommendation.</string>
    <string name="title_food4">The Big Chill</string>
    <string name="address_food4">311,312- 314, 2nd Floor, DLF Promenade Mall, Vasant Kunj II, New Delhi, Delhi 110070</string>
    <string name="phone_food4"> 011 4875 0000</string>
    <string name="time_food4">12:00 PM - 11:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_food4">This is a place where grandparents, toddlers and everyone in between feel a sense of belonging. Shakes, ice creams made from natural fruits, malted drinks and pizzas, salads and the most decadent cakes are all popular choices, while you listen to 70s music and scream to make yourself heard over the din.People love pasta in red wine sauce, oreo mousse cheesecake the most at The Big Chill.Main cuisine served at The Big Chill is Casual Eclectic.</string>
    <string name="title_food5">Masala Library by Jiggs Kalra</string>
    <string name="address_food5">21A, Near Le Meridian, Janpath, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="phone_food5">092051 80003</string>
    <string name="time_food5">12:00 PM - 2:30 PM  , 7 PM - 11:30 PM</string>
    <string name="body_food5">Masala Library is located in the very heart of the city, just beside Meridien Hotel and on one of the most storied roads of New Delhi, bang on Janpath. The restaurant is notable for its deconstructed food, location, and the superb tasting menu; founded by Maestro Jiggs Kalra and his dynamic son Zorawar, the chefs infuse diners\' palate is imploded with the 33 courses of molecular gastronomy in a large, well lit, 90 seater space with beautiful interior. Must Try:Radhuni sea bass with pui saag. Dcor is kept simple to avoid distractions from the innovative progressive Indian fare. Central light console and a staircase accessible wine cellar, white tablecloths and solid cutlery complete the luxurious dining feel.There are many conventional dishes vegetarian options but Masala library is not consistent. A number of dishes\' creativity tips over into gimmickry and a few with the brilliant concept falters in execution. The food is good and very expensive to dine here.</string>
    <string name="title_food6">Bukhara</string>
    <string name="address_food6">ITC Maurya, Diplomatic Enclave, Sardar Patel Marg, Chanakyapuri, New Delhi</string>
    <string name="phone_food6">011 4621 5124</string>
    <string name="time_food6">12:30 PM - 02:45 PM  ,  07:00 PM - 11:45 PM</string>
    <string name="body_food6">The historic and classic Bukhara is ensconced in one of the premier elite hotels namely ITC Maurya. It is a wonderful fine dining restaurant acclaimed for its high quality of delicious North Indian food prepared in the traditional clay oven. The elegant environs of this plush restaurant are created by artistically done interiors in vibrant hues of ochre and brown. It is an amazing and famous specialty restaurant for food enthusiasts who like to have mouthwatering Mughlai food amidst sophisticated environs where you can entertain your prestigious guests. The indoor seating arrangement of this iconic eating place is comfortable and thus makes the legendary restaurant perfect not only for family dinner and lunch but for pampering your important business associates with super delicious food and drinks. Bukhara in New Delhi is a must visit for authentic barbeque food and Biryani lovers. The rich aroma of the barbeque delicacies is simply tempting and awesome. The lavish spread of Mughlai dishes are cooked in traditional style using authentic ingredients and thus retain original flavors. Bukhara offers a wonderful medley of luscious mutton and kebabs. Do not miss their flavorsome Mutton Biryani, mouth melting Chicken Bukhara with no artificial food colour, delicious Raan, sumptuous Butter Chicken, Champ Tajdar, soft Burrah Kebab, Tandoori Pomfret, Rarah Meat served with Ulta tawa Paranthas and crisp Naan .Widely known as a \'Meat Lovers Haunt\' Bukhara also serves delicious dishes to Vegetarian guests including authentic tandoori Guchhi, Creamy Dal Bukhara, tandoori Gobi, Tandoori Simla mirch, delicious Sarson ka Saag and delectable Makkai ki Roti. Interesting vegan options and special gluten free options are also available for diners with specific food preferences. Lip-smacking desserts include delicious Gulab jamun, cool Rasmali, yummy Phirni and melting maringe tarts. The quality of food is remarkable as fresh herbs and ingredients are used to impart authentic flavor and taste to the food.</string>
    <string name="title_food7">Hauz Khas Social</string>
    <string name="address_food7">9A &amp; 12, Hauz Khas Fort Rd, Deer Park, New Delhi, Delhi 110016</string>
    <string name="phone_food7">078386 52814</string>
    <string name="time_food7">12:00 PM - 12:00 AM</string>
    <string name="body_food7">Hauz Khas Social is one of the prettiest nightspots in town and takes full advantage of its lush, history-soaked location, which makes it hardest places to get into on weekends. Within touching distance of the reservoir in Hauz Khas Village, South Delhi, Hauz Khas Social is just the place to blend mood and nightlife.No matter what you feel like drinking, we assure you Hauz Khas Social will have it. An impressive selection of beers, malts and signature cocktails pulls even the staunchest of tipplers to Socials doorstep. Artisan cocktails are their USP and worth checking out. Food-wise, Hauz Khas Social is designed to amaze. Their food menu is eclectic, varied and brimming with comforting innovation. This is one of the few bars in the city to serve breakfast. After you get your drink, order yourself a few appetizers. Binge on, momos from hell, pork belly pops, croquettish, Joses jalapeno chicken tikka, gunpowder calamari, death wings, almond Tikki chaat, and fish tacos. The culinary fun continues with an assortment of mains like, chilly &amp; black pepper chicken bao, OMG burger, Black Label butter chicken, 4 cheese pizza, grilled chicken peri-peri sizzler, Social keema spaghetti, and Burmese Khao suey. Live music in evenings keeps the mood elevated.</string>
    <string name="title_food8">Bikanervala</string>
    <string name="address_food8">D – 158, Kamla Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi 110007</string>
    <string name="phone_food8"> 095601 77933</string>
    <string name="time_food8">8:00 AM - 11:00 PM</string>
    <string name="body_food8">Bikanervala, situated in Kamla Nagar, North Delhi is a true paradise for vegetarians and people who love fast food and street food. Specializing in North Indian cuisine and sweets. Whether you want to enjoy a scrumptious breakfast or enjoy some street food, Bikanervala has it all. The professional staff, prompt service, and beautiful ambiance make Bikanervala an ideal family restaurant. Whether you want to fulfill your craving for a spicy chat or some mouthwatering desserts, Bikanervala is the right place for you. The affordable pricing makes it an ideal family restaurant.</string>
    <string name="title_food9">Gulati Restaurant</string>
    <string name="address_food9">6, Pandara Rd, Pandara Flats, Market, New Delhi, Delhi 110003</string>
    <string name="phone_food9"> 011 2378 2949</string>
    <string name="time_food9">12:00 PM - 10:00 PM</string>
    <string name="body_food9">At its heart, Gulati is a middle-class dining option that has achieved stardom. Tourist groups from overseas have been known to book half the restaurant for lunch. The murgh tikka and tandoori murgh are two best-selling starters, while murgh makhni, gosht achari and magaz masala are popular main-course choices.</string>
    <string name="title_food10">Naivedyam</string>
    <string name="address_food10">1, Hauz Khas Village, Deer Park, Hauz Khas, New Delhi, Delhi 110016</string>
    <string name="phone_food10"> 011 2696 0426</string>
    <string name="time_food10">10:00 AM - 11:00 PM</string>
    <string name="body_food10">Naivedyam is a famous chain of south indian cousine restaurants.Must Try: Thali, Mysore Masala Dosa, Filtered Coffee, Rava Dosa, Dahi Vada, Buttermilk, Chaach. Known For its artsy, peaceful ambiance and South Indian food</string>

    <string name="title_shop1">Select CITYWALK</string>
    <string name="address_shop1">A-3, Saket District Centre, District Centre, Sector 6, Pushp Vihar, New Delhi, Delhi 110017</string>
    <string name="body_shop1">Select CITYWALK is one of the top malls of Delhi. Spread over 6 acres, the chic shopping centre houses more than 500 Indian and international brands which include Tommy Hilfiger, Calvin and Klein, Charles and Keith, Aldo, United Colors of Benneton, Pantaloons, Pepe Jeans Mango among others. The mall also has an extensive range of international chains and numerous interesting restaurants where you can satiate your taste buds with host of cuisines ranging from Chinese and Thai to Italian, Indian and Arabic/Lebanese. For entertainment, there is PVR Cinemas where you can get weekly dose of Bollywood masala and Hollywood action. Head to Select CITYWALK, a one-stop destination to shop, eat, be entertained and have a good time.</string>
    <string name="title_shop2">Ambience Mall</string>
    <string name="address_shop2">Plot No, 2, Nelson Mandela Marg, Ambience Island, Vasant Kunj II, Vasant Kunj, New Delhi, Delhi 110070</string>
    <string name="body_shop2">Ambience Mall, Vasant Kunj is an apogee of lifestyle distinction. We offer an experience of unparalleled retail mix combined with entertainment and leisure attractions that has changed the concept of shopping mall experience.</string>
    <string name="title_shop3">Pacific Mall</string>
    <string name="address_shop3">Najafgarh Rd, Tagore Garden, Tilak Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi 110018</string>
    <string name="body_shop3">A visit to Pacific Mall always ends with living up to the phrase \'shop till you drop\'. Some of our favourite stores are Call It Spring (for Aldo-style shoes and accessories but at a lower price range), Store 99 (to score quirky stationary and homeware), Zara, Charles &amp; Keith, Forest Essentials, and Spar which is a hypermarket that has everything including groceries, toys, utensils and even basic t-shirts and jeans. Along with an impressive line-up of stores, their entertainment options are awesome as well.This huge mall is always bustling and is a good place to shop and hang out at (especially if you\'re feeling too lazy to make more elaborate plans). If you\'re visiting by the metro, the closest station is Subhash Nagar on the blue line.  </string>
    <string name="title_shop4">DLF Promenade</string>
    <string name="address_shop4"> 3 Nelson Mandela Road, Vasant Kunj Mall Road, Vasant Kunj, New Delhi, Delhi 110070</string>
    <string name="body_shop4">Well maintained, with many food options and all major clothing brands.Huge variety of shopping Stores, brands and food outlets. This mall is a pleasure to shop and eat in , since it\'s never too crowded and is spread out in multiple floors. Apart from the valet parking( to help you park) one can browse and shop around (without being pushed around by other shoppers) and then eat in any of the food joints above.</string>
    <string name="title_shop5">Connaught Place</string>
    <string name="address_shop5">Hanuman Road Area, Connaught Place, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="body_shop5">Connaught Place is a frenetic business and financial hub, centered on a ring of colonnaded Georgian-style buildings with global chain stores, vintage cinemas, bars and Indian restaurants. Stalls at Connaught Place Market sell saris, embroidered bags and trinkets.</string>
    <string name="title_shop6">The Chanakya</string>
    <string name="address_shop6">Yashwant Place Commercial Complex Opposite Chanakyapuri Post Office, Chanakyapuri, New Delhi, Delhi 110021</string>
    <string name="body_shop6">Sophisticated shopping mall featuring international luxury brands, a gourmet food court and multiplex. Very exclusive yet inviting. Attractive and modern design. The shops and food court are all well-appointed and tastefully decorated.If you\'re the kind of man who loves all things fancy, shopping at The Chanakya Mall would probably be a great idea. From Ralph Lauren to Nicobar, we\'ve listed out all the brands that are worth your time and money. </string>
    <string name="title_shop7">Lajpat Market</string>
    <string name="address_shop7">K-47, Mata Naina Devi Marg, Central Market, Lajpat Nagar II, Lajpat Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi 110024</string>
    <string name="body_shop7">Lajpat Nagar is famous for its Central Market, a popular shopping destination, and also is known for the garments and textiles which are sold there. The charm of Lajpat Nagar market lies in its location and posh environment and its high end stores for ethnic wear.</string>
    <string name="title_shop8">Dilli Haat</string>
    <string name="address_shop8"> INA Market, Dilli Haat, Kidwai Nagar West, Kidwai Nagar, Delhi, 110023</string>
    <string name="body_shop8">Dilli Haat is a paid-entrance open-air food plaza and craft bazaar located in Delhi, run by Delhi Tourism and Transportation Development Corporation. Unlike the traditional weekly market, the village Haat, Dilli Haat is permanent. It is located in the commercial centres of South Delhi, opposite INA market.Dilli Haat, has been specifically set up by the government to provide a platform for artisans to come and sell their wares. It gives the feel of a traditional weekly village market (called a haat) and offers cultural performances and Indian cuisine as well. The concept is hugely popular.</string>
    <string name="title_shop9">Sarojini Market</string>
    <string name="address_shop9">Sarojini Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi 110023</string>
    <string name="body_shop9">Sarojini nagar market is located in the south west district of Delhi.It is very much developed market and is the cleanest and popular market.In this market clothes and shoes are sold at very reasonable price. It is the best place for shopping lovers who do not look for branded items. Sarojini Nagar market is famous for clothes shopping, decorative items and cheap backpacks. The market also boasts of its wide range of home decor items like cushions, cushion covers, paintings and fancy lamps.</string>
    <string name="title_shop10">Janpath &amp; Tibetan Market</string>
    <string name="address_shop10">Janpath Rd, Janpath, Connaught Place, New Delhi, Delhi 110001</string>
    <string name="body_shop10">Janpath Market is one of the most famous markets for tourists (both Indian and foreign) in New Delhi. The market essentially is a long line of boutique stores selling products which are hard to find in the malls and multi-chain stores of the city.Relatively less known to some people but teeming with life and a great experience. These markets are good for bargains on leather goods, clothes and jewellery. Tibetan eateries serve up great food! If you are a book lover, you could end up with some great books at super prices!</string>

    <string name="title_hotel1">Four Points by Sheraton</string>
    <string name="address_hotel1"> Plot no 9, National Highway - 8, D Block, Samalka, New Delhi, Delhi 110037</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel1"> 011 6604 0000</string>
    <string name="body_hotel1">Set 4.8 km from Indira Gandhi International Airport, this upscale hotel surrounded by lawns and gardens is 12 km from Chhatarpur Templeand 16 km from the Connaught Place business district.Modern rooms have hardwood floors, free Wi-Fi and 40-inch flat-screen TVs, as well as minibars, and teaand coffeemaking facilities. Upgraded rooms include sitting areas and/or pool views. Room service is available 24/7.Breakfast and parking are complimentary.There\'s a casual international restaurant with floor-to-ceiling windows, and a streamlined bar. Other amenities include a fitness room and an outdoor pool.</string>
    <string name="title_hotel2">The Muse Sarovar Portico</string>
    <string name="address_hotel2">88-89, Bijwasan Rd, Kapas Hera Extension, Kapas Hera, New Delhi, Delhi 110037</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel2"> 011 4909 9999</string>
    <string name="body_hotel2">This relaxed hotel in a modern building on a palm-fringed plot is 20 km from Qutb Minar, a 12th-century minaret in a UNESCO WorldHeritage Site, and 6 km from Indira Gandhi International Airport.Warmly decorated rooms with wood accents offer free Wi-Fi and flat-screen TVs, as well as minibars, safes, and tea and coffee making facilities; some have sitting areas. Upgraded rooms include limited meeting room use. Room service is offered 24/7.Breakfast and parking are complimentary. Other amenities include an all-day restaurant, and a casual eatery in the airy atrium, as well as an outdoor pool and a gym. Meeting space is available.</string>
    <string name="title_hotel3">Shervani Nehru Place</string>
    <string name="address_hotel3">B-20, Chirag Enclave Rd, Chirag Enclave, Nehru Place, New Delhi, Delhi 110048</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel3"> 011 4680 1000</string>
    <string name="body_hotel3">This informal hotel is a 2-minute walk from a monorail station, 2 km from the iconic, flower-shaped Lotus Temple and 4 km from Okhla Industrial Area.Featuring neutral tones and wood decor, the relaxed rooms come with free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs, and tea and coffee making facilities. Club rooms grant lounge access for drinks and snacks; upgraded club quarters also offer sitting areas and sofa beds. Room service is available 24/7.A breakfast buffet and parking are complimentary. Dining options include a restaurant, and a lounge serving light bites. Other amenities consist of an outdoor pool, an exercise room and a terrace.</string>
    <string name="title_hotel4">Calista Resort</string>
    <string name="address_hotel4">37/2-4 Old, NH 48, Kapas Hera, New Delhi, Delhi 110037</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel4"> 011 4103 4591</string>
    <string name="body_hotel4">This refined, family-run hotel is 7 km from Indira Gandhi International Airport and 22 km from the iconic India Gate.Warmly furnished rooms feature minibars, flat-screen TVs and free Wi-Fi, as well as tea and coffee making facilities. Upgraded rooms add sitting areas. Room service is available 24/7.Parking is complimentary. Dining options include an upscale international restaurant and a relaxed coffee shop. A doctor is on-call. Airport transfers are offered for a surcharge.</string>
    <string name="title_hotel5">Hotel Saket 27</string>
    <string name="address_hotel5"> J-27, Saket, New Delhi, Delhi 110017</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel5">011 4797 4797</string>
    <string name="body_hotel5">A 4-minute walk from the nearest bus stop, this down-to-earth hotel in an upscale residential district is also 3.2 km from Qutb Minar tower and 7 km from Lotus Temple.Featuring wooden floors, the understated rooms come with free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and minibars, plus tea and coffeemakers. Some offer sofas. Room service is also available.Breakfast and valet parking are free. There\'s also a casual restaurant serving international cuisine. Other amenities include a gym and a business centre, plus meeting rooms and event space.</string>
    <string name="title_hotel6">The Suryaa </string>
    <string name="address_hotel6">Friends Colony West, New Friends Colony, New Delhi, Delhi 110025</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel6"> 011 4780 8080</string>
    <string name="body_hotel6">This stylish hotel is a 9-minute walk from Sukhdev Vihar metro station, 3 km from the Lotus Temple and 6 km from Humayun\'s Tomb.Warm, relaxed rooms feature flat-screens, safes and sitting areas, plus tea and coffee making facilities. Suites add separate living areas. Room service and Wi-Fi are available.Parking is free. Other amenities include 2 restaurants, a French cafe and an opulent lobby bar, as well as an outdoor pool, a spa and a gym. There\'s also meeting and event space. A breakfast buffet is available for a fee.</string>
    <string name="title_hotel7">Radisson Blu Plaza</string>
    <string name="address_hotel7">NH-8, near Mahipalpur Extension, Block R, Mahipalpur Village, Delhi Cantonment, New Delhi, Delhi 110037</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel7">011 2677 9191</string>
    <string name="body_hotel7">Set in the bustling business district, this upmarket hotel is 2.3 km from Indira Gandhi International Airport. It’s also 4.8 km from shopping at Ambiance Mall and 11 km from live entertainment at Kingdom of Dreams.The warm rooms and suites feature free Wi-Fi and flat-screen TVs, plus wood floors, work stations and sofas. Upgraded rooms include minibars and access to a private lounge, while suites add separate living rooms.Free breakfast is served. There are 4 dining options, plus a pastry shop, a lounge and a wine bar. Massages and therapeutic treatments are available in the spa. There’s a gym, plus an outdoor pool, a sauna and a steam room.</string>
    <string name="title_hotel8">Taj Palace</string>
    <string name="address_hotel8">2, Sardar Patel Marg, Diplomatic Enclave, Chanakyapuri, New Delhi, Delhi 110021</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel8">011 2611 0202</string>
    <string name="body_hotel8">The hotel is 2.2 mi from Rashtrapati Bhavan, 3.5 mi from Jantar Mantar and 3.8 mi from India Gate. Delhi International Airport is a 15-minute drive.Spread over six acres of lush gardens, offering an outdoor swimming pool and panoramic city views, Taj Palace New Delhi is located in New Delhi. WiFi access is available.Couples in particular like the location – they rated it 9.0 for a two-person trip.Each room here will provide you with air conditioning and a mini-bar. There is also an electric kettle. Featuring a shower, private bathroom also comes with a bath and a hairdryer.</string>
    <string name="title_hotel9">The Leela Palace </string>
    <string name="address_hotel9">Africa Ave, Diplomatic Enclave, Chanakyapuri, New Delhi, Delhi 110023</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel9"> 011 3933 1234</string>
    <string name="body_hotel9">This upmarket hotel is 5 km from Lodhi Garden, Safdarjung Tomb and the Gandhi Smriti museum.Opulent rooms offer free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and marble bathrooms, plus sitting areas, and tea and coffeemaking facilities. Suites add separate living areas and butler service; some have plunge pools, private gyms and/or Jacuzzis. Upgraded quarters provide access to a club lounge with complimentary drinks and snacks.Dining options consist of 4 restaurants, a refined bar and a cafe with regular live music. Other amenities include a rooftop infinity pool, event space, and a spa with a gym and a sauna. Breakfast is available.</string>
    <string name="title_hotel10">JW Marriott Hotel</string>
    <string name="address_hotel10"> Asset Area 4 - Hospitality District Delhi, Aerocity, New Delhi, Delhi 110037</string>
    <string name="phone_hotel10"> 011 4521 2121</string>
    <string name="body_hotel10">This sophisticated hotel is an 8-minute walk from Delhi Aerocity metro station and 2.5 km from Indira Gandhi International Airport\'s terminals.Sleek, contemporary rooms offer flat-screen TVs, Wi-Fi (fee), minifridges, and tea and coffeemaking facilities. Some add balconies; club rooms include access to a lounge with free drinks. Suites feature integrated or separate living areas.There\'s a breakfast buffet (fee) and a pair of restaurants for international cuisine, plus a cafe/bakery, and a lounge bar with live entertainment. Amenities include a heated outdoor pool, a fitness centre and a spa, plus 8 function rooms.</string>
    <string name="favourites">favourites</string>
</resources>
